pizzabolis.com 2017-07-12

# Pizza Boli's: We Deliver MORE! - Privacy Policy

## Prosperity System, Inc. Privacy Policy

Prosperity System, Inc. d/b/a Pizza Boli's ("PSI," "We," "Us," or "Our) is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information that you may provide to Us on this website (the "Site"). This notice describes our Privacy Policy. **By visiting this Site, you are accepting the Privacy Policy described below. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should immediately cease the use of this Site.**

### 1\. What Personal Information Do We Collect?

**Personal Information You Provide.** We collect information that you voluntarily provide on online forms, including user and e-club registration, sweepstakes registration, contact requests, guest comments, online surveys, online orders, and other online activities. The personal information ("Personal Information") that we collect may include some or all of the following: your name, address, telephone number, email address, text messaging information and other contact information associated with electronic or digital messaging methods, credit card information, demographic information or any other information that you voluntarily provide to us. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features.

**Cookies.** Like many websites, we use "cookies." Cookies are small programs that we transfer to your hard drive that allow us to recognize you and to provide you with a customized experience each time you visit. If you do not want us to use cookies, you can easily disable them by going to the toolbar of your web browser and clicking on the "Help" button. Follow the instructions that will prevent the browser from accepting cookies, or set the browser to inform you when you receive a new cookie. In addition, you may visit this and other websites anonymously through the use of utilities provided by other private companies.

If you disable the cookies, some parts of the Site and some of the services may be more difficult or impossible to use.

**Other Information.** Every computer has an IP (Internet Protocol) address. IP addresses of computers used to visit this site are noted. In addition, we automatically collect other information such as email addresses, browser types, operating systems, and the URL addresses of sites clicked to and from this site.

### 2\. How Do We Use Your Personal Information?

We may use your Personal Information to administer our business activities, which include providing customer service; contacting you concerning an order; and making other products and services available to you. We may share your Personal Information with our affiliates, subsidiaries, contractors and franchisees as necessary to further these business activities and to serve you.

We may share Personal Information with applicable law enforcement authorities if necessary to comply with a court order, subpoena, government investigation or other legal requirement.

We may share Personal Information with third parties in the event of a sale, merger, acquisition or other corporate event.

### 3\. How Can You Control the Use of Your Personal Information?

It is your choice whether you receive emails or special offers from us or others by setting your preferences in your online profile. If you wish to change your preferences or stop receiving emails from us, you may do so at any time by updating your online profile or contact us at [info@pizzabolis.com](mailto:info@pizzabolis.com "info@pizzabolis.com").

### 4\. How do We Protect the Privacy of Children?

Online ordering, customer registration for online ordering, and customer feedback pages are directed toward and designed for use by persons aged 13 or older. We do not establish or maintain registrations for any child whom we know to be under the age of 13. We do not solicit or knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we discover that we have received Personal Information from an individual who indicates that he or she is, or whom we otherwise have reason to believe is, under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our systems.

### 5\. How Does our Site Interact with Third-Party Websites?

We may provide links to various third-party websites from this Site. If you link to another site, **your privacy depends on the policy of that site**. We strongly urge you to check their privacy policy. Not all sites guarantee that they will not share your personally identifiable information with others.

### 6\. How Can you Contact Us?

We want you to enjoy your Pizza Boli's experience and your use of the Site. If you have any questions, or believe that a violation of this Privacy Policy has occurred, please contact us at [info@pizzabolis.com](mailto:info@pizzabolis.com "info@pizzabolis.com").

We reserve the right to modify this policy in the future. If we do so, we will post a notice on our home page.

Effective: October 1, 2010

©2017 Prosperity System, Inc. All rights reserved.
